Burden of Dreams is a documentary film directed by Les Blank.
The Amazon rain forest, 1979.
The crew of Fitzcarraldo (1982), a film directed by German director Werner Herzog, soon finds itself with problems related to casting, tribal struggles and accidents, among many
other setbacks; but nothing compared to dragging a huge steamboat up a mountain, while Herzog embraces the path of a certain madness to make his vision come true.
Self - Narrator (voice), played by Candace Laughlin.
Self - Filmmaker, played by Werner Herzog.
Self - Actor, played by Klaus Kinski.
Self - Actress, played by Claudia Cardinale.
Self, played by Alfredo de Río Tambo.
Self, played by Ángela Reina.
Burden of Dreams is a 1982 documentary film directed and produced by Les Blank.
The film explores themes of cinema on cinema, movie business,
amazon rainforest, behind the scenes, anthropology.